arsenalnews.net 2019-06-01

# Arsenal News - Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 

• To send periodic emails 

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and keep track of advertisements and . 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page. 

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [ http://www.arsenalnews.net](http://www.arsenalnews.net/)

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.  

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on 07/02/2009  

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Skweet Ltd  
2nd Floor  
145-157 St John Street  
London  
EC1V 4PY  
United Kingdom  
<http://www.skweet.co.uk/>
